ryobitools.eu 2014-03-25

# Designed to do more Privacy Policy | Ryobi Tools

**Internet Privacy Techtronic Industries ELC GmbH**

**Privacy Policy**

We appreciate your interest in our company and our products and we want you to feel secure about the protection of your personal information when visiting our website. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. The compliance with the relevant data protection law is for us an obligation / a matter of course.

All data processing operations (collection, processing and use) by the Techtronic Industries ELC GmbH comply strictly with the statutory data protection regulations. We collect process and use personal data to carry out orders or purchase orders and in order to improve the content and functionality of our services.

**Personal data and its use**

We need personal data in following cases:

• for purchase order  
• for the implementation of orders  
• When contacting us (employees, applicants, interested parties, customers, suppliers)

We record primarily personal information for the business and order processing. To this end, we forward personal information to third parties who act for or on behalf of Techtronic Industries ELC GmbH (§ 11 BDSG, order data management). These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for purposes other than those to which we inform you in this statement. To prevent the misuse of our websites, when you visit our websites we collect by default different information (such as the IP address, time and duration, operating system, browser, page view).

**Security of data**

To protect the personal information of our customers, we process the data only on data centers and computers protected by security technologies fulfilling the industry-standard (e.g. firewalls, password protection, access controls, etc.). We record personal data only as long as necessary for the purposes for which it was collected, or to comply with legal requirements on reporting or document retention. Safety precautions All employees of our company are committed to privacy by the applicable data protection law. Our data center as well as the in-house IT department adapt the technical security measures continuously to the current circumstances and requirements. Both are subject to constant monitoring by the Data Protection Commissioner.

**Data Access and Corrections**

According to the Federal Data Protection Act you have the right to free information about your stored data, and the right to correct, block or delete such data. Exceptions to this are data which correction, blocking or deletion is conflicting with statutory or contractual retention period, furthermore data necessary for the establishment, for the content, or change of your contractual relationship with us or are required to be stored for accounting purposes.

If you have any questions regarding the use of your data, you will be directed to our Privacy Officer.

**Techtronic Industries ELC GmbH**  
Herrn Thomas Fletschinger  
Max-Eyth-Strasse 10  
71364 Winnenden / Germany  
E-Mail: dsb@TTI-EMEA.com

**Hyperlinks to other websites**

Some of our web pages contain links to other websites which are not operated by Techtronic Industries ELC GmbH. We monitor these websites and are not responsible for their content nor for their handling of personal information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will update this Statement of Privacy (if necessary) on the basis of current circumstances, such as a change in the relevant data protection legislation.

State of the Declaration: August 2012
